1. Statement - alias_exists = false
5. callTestCase
1. Statement - currentUrl = ""
5. Statement - Try
1. Statement - currentUrl = com.kms.katalon.core.webui.keyword.WebUiBuiltInKeywords.getUrl()
2. openBrowser
6. maximizeWindow
10. Statement - currentUrl = com.kms.katalon.core.webui.keyword.WebUiBuiltInKeywords.getUrl()
9. Statement - If (!(currentUrl.equals(url)))
13. Statement - Try
1. verifyTextPresent
17. verifyTextPresent
11. Chekc if a frame with the same alias exist on the "Adresses page". If so, a delete button normaly also exists. And in this case, we will expect an error message after clicking the add address button
15. Statement - If (com.kms.katalon.core.webui.keyword.WebUiBuiltInKeywords.waitForElementPresent(deleteButton, 2))
19. click